<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ToiceExam</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string-array name="theme">
        <item>Default</item>
        <item>Dark</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="rules">Tài khoản khách hàng được tạo ra trên App, sau lần đầu tiên đăng nhập vào tài khoản,
        khách hàng tự chịu trách nhiệm về năng lực hành vi trong việc thay đổi thông tin cá nhân và sử dụng.
        Việc thu thập dữ liệu chủ yếu trên App bao gồm: email, điện thoại, tên đăng nhập, mật khẩu đăng nhập, địa chỉ khách hàng.
        Đây là các thông tin mà App cần khách hàng bắt buộc khi đăng ký sử dụng dịch vụ y tế và để App liên hệ xác nhận khi khách hàng
        đăng ký sử dụng dịch vụ trên app nhằm đảm bảo quyền lợi cho cho khách hàng.Trong quá trình sử dụng dịch vụ y tế trên App,
        chúng tôi lưu giữ thông tin chi tiết về lịch sử đặt lịch hẹn, bệnh án điện tử, đơn thuốc (nếu có), tiểu sử bệnh lý.
        Các khách hàng sẽ tự chịu trách nhiệm về bảo mật và lưu giữ mọi hoạt động sử dụng dịch vụ y tế dưới tên đăng ký, mật khẩu của mình.
        Ngoài ra, khách hàng có trách nhiệm thông báo kịp thời về App về những hành vi sử dụng trái phép, lạm dụng, vi phạm bảo mật,
        lưu giữ tên đăng ký và mật khẩu của bên thứ ba để có biện pháp giải quyết phù hợp.</string>

    //navagation bar bottom
    <string name="title_exam">Exam</string>
    <string name="title_home_bar">home</string>
    <string name="title_setting">setting</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="paragraph">"Just a reminder that the charity barbecue is happening this Friday! It is for a good cause;
        we're __(1)__ money for the children's charity Future Horizons to buy computers for community centers in disadvantaged neighborhoods,
        so please come along and help out!  It will be at 7:30 at Oak Park, next to the gazebo by the west gate. Dinner will be 15 dollars
        and there will be hamburgers, hotdogs, or veggie burgers, and of course a lots of salads and desserts! Bring your family and friends;
        everyone __(2)__ welcome. Please get tickets from me or from Sophia Johnson.  I hope __(3)__ you there!  Jane Anderson "</string>

    <string name="P1">For each question, you will see a picture and you will hear four short statements.
        The statements will be spoken just one time. They will not be printed in your test book so you must listen carefully
        to understand what the speaker says. When you hear the four statements, look at the picture and choose the statement
        that best describes what you see in the picture. Choose the best answer A, B, C or D</string>

    <string name="P2">In this part of the test, you will hear a question or statement spoken in English, followed by three responses,
        also spoken in English. The question or statement and the responses will be spoken just one time. They will not be printed in your test book,
        so you must listen carefully. You are to choose the best response to each question or statement. Now listen to a sample question.</string>

    <string name="P3">You will hear some conversations between two people. You will be asked to answer three questions about what the speakers
        say in each conversation. Select the best response to each question and mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet.
        The conversations will not be printed in your test book and will be spoken only one time.</string>

    <string name="P4">You will hear some talks given by a single speaker. You will be asked to answer three questions about what
        the speaker says in each talk. Select the best response to each question and mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet.
        The talks will not be printed in your test book and will be spoken only one time.</string>

    <string name="P5">You will hear some conversations between two people. You will be asked to answer three questions about what the
        speakers say in each conversation. Select the best response to each question and mark the letter A, B , C or D on your answer sheet.
        The conversations will not be printed in your test book and will be spoken only one time.</string>

    <string name="P6">Read the texts that follow. A word or pharse is missing in some of the sentences. Four answer choices are given below
        each of the sentences. Select the best answer to complete the text. Then mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet.</string>

    <string name="P7">In this part you will read a selection of texts, such as magezine and newspaper articles, letters, and advertisements.
        Each text is followed by several questions. Select the best answer for each question and mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet.</string>
</resources>